《绿箭》前情回顾
Previously, on "Arrow"...
我找到我们那位惊悚先生的身份了
I got an ID on our Mr. Creepy.
我不知道这符号是什么意思
I'm not sure what that symbol means.
这代表混乱
It means anarchy.
■
本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译
最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv
朗尼·马尚
Lonnie Machin.
全职的疯子
Full time crazy pants.
翻译   Z小花儿 小暴徒 SophiaSaaaga
快手  不要
Speedy, don't!
翻译    阿噻 桃子西 PiPi TvYoung
有时
Sometimes,
教训人最好的办法不是惩罚他们
the best way to teach someone a lesson isn't to punish them;
校对   苹果果  Z小花儿  Reginamoon
精校   陈小圈
而是惩罚他们最在乎的人
it's to punish the ones he cares about the most.
费利西蒂·斯莫克
Felicity Smoak...
时间轴风吹来的那片云
你愿意让我
would you make me
成为地球上最幸福的男人吗
the happiest man on the face of the earth?
特效&后期   咖啡Lee[绿箭侠]       总监   苹果果
我愿意
Yes!
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
四个月后
现在我知道
Now I know...
这不是我的错
that it's not my fault.
是我的责任
It's my responsibility.
责任  什么责任
Responsibility? To do what?
结束这一切
To end it.
我要杀了他
I'm going to kill him.
现在
达克在哪里
Where is Darhk?!
绿 箭
第四季  第十集
有线索吗
Any luck?
都是些宁死也不肯开口的幽灵
Just more ghosts who would rather die than talk.
没人供出达克的行踪
Nobody--nobody is going to give up Darhk.
约翰  我们还得找安迪谈谈
John, we got to talk to Andy again.
我觉得安迪不会配合
I don't think Andy is in a very cooperative place.
达克已经不见踪迹了
Darhk is gone to ground.
现在  除非形式转变
Right now, unless things change,
否则安迪就是我们抓住他的最佳机会
Andy is our best chance of catching him.
费利西蒂准备做另一场手术
Felicity's going in for another surgery.
我们要是快点
If we hurry,
或许能赶在她进去准备前见她一面
we might be able to see her before she goes into prep.
不  不  还没抓住达克
No. No. Darhk's in the wind.
等得越久  就更难抓到他
The longer he's there, the harder he's going to be to catch.
我要留在这里
I'm going to stay here,
看看匿名热线有没有可用的线索
find something useful from the tip line.
费利西蒂会希望我这么做的
It's what Felicity would want me to do.
别想就这样骗到我  伙计
Can't lie your way out of this one, pal.
之前瑞特或许信了你编的故事
Reiter might have bought your B.S. before,
但现在有了这些地图
but now, with these maps,
这位乌克兰小姐也还活着
and ol' Miss Ukraine over here still being alive,
你没戏了
it's game over.
他需要休息一会儿
He needs to rest-- for a moment.
我不管  继续前进
Don't care. Keep movin'.
等他晕过去了  你是打算杀了他吗
And when he passes out, do you plan on killing him?
好吧  快点
Fine. Quick.
你得逃走
You need to make a run for it.
我去引开康克林
I'll distract Conklin.
怎么引开  用血流不止吓唬他吗
By doing what? Bleeding on him?
真叫人感动啊
Well, isn't this touching?
好了  起来  我们走
All right, come on, let's go.
别对他用情太深  亲爱的
Don't get too attached to him, sweetheart.
他长命百岁的几率可不大
His prospects for a long life don't look too good.
感觉怎样
How are you feeling?
我完全准备好了
I have never been more ready
让一群家伙折腾我的身体
to have a bunch of guys poking around inside me.
我是说医生
Doctors.
做医生该做的
Doing doctor things.
他们相信之前的手术能修复神经损伤  所以
They think the last surgery will fix the nerve damage, so.
这是奥利弗送给你的
These are from Oliver.
他能路过一下真是太好了
Well, that's really nice of him to stop by.
没关系
Yeah, it's ok.
我知道他在竭尽全力去搜寻...
I know he's doing everything he can to track down the, uh...
这些花
flowers.
那件事重要得多
Which is much more important.
而且  有你们在这里就够了
Plus, I got all the support I need right here.
费利西蒂
Felicity?
该准备做手术了
I'm here to prep you for surgery.
我会没事的
I'm going to be fine.
你难道不觉得烦吗
Aren't you tired of this?
依旧是没有结果的谈话
Same dead end conversation.
我不会说  也不会帮你
I'm not talking, I'm not helping.
别再浪费彼此的时间了
So how about you stop wasting both our time?
绿箭侠要我来找你聊聊达克的事
The Green Arrow told me to have a conversation with you about Darhk.
真没看出来啊  约翰
I'm surprised, John.
没想到你还有这魄力
I didn't think you had it in you.
-我也没想到  -那是什么不一样了
- I didn't. ‭- So what changed?
因为费利西蒂出事了
Her name is Felicity.
星城警局
好  听着  我知道  好吗
Yeah, listen, I know, I know, all right?
做就是了
Just--just do--
听着  我得等会儿再打给你  等会聊
Listen, I got to call you back, call you back.
她怎么样了
How's she doing?
她又在动手术
She's in surgery again.
那你过来干什么
Then what are you doing here?
搜寻达米恩·达克
Looking for Damian Darhk.
有一张
There's a card
我们还没亮出的牌
that we haven't turned over yet,
之所以没亮这张牌
and we haven't turned it over,
是因为一旦亮牌了
because when we do,
他就会知道你是我们一伙的
he will know that you are working with us.
你想知道我和达克见面的地方
You want to know where I've been meeting with Darhk.
对
Yeah.
你会回不了家
You won't be able to go home.
幸好避难室还有地方
Luckily, we have space in the bunker.
有可以住人的地方
There are living quarters.
劳蕾尔怎么办
What about Laurel?
她能照顾好自己
She can take care of herself.
是啊  她没问题
Yeah, she can do that.
好吧  第六大街832号  办公楼第30层
Alright--office building, 832 Sixth Street, 30th floor.
可费利西蒂在医院
But with Felicity in the hospital,
我和劳蕾尔留守阵地
me and Laurel watching our backs,
你的队伍战斗力就弱了
your team gets mighty small.
只要能抓住达克  这些都不重要
None of it matters once Darhk is off the board.
所以你又要大开杀戒了
So you're back to dropping bodies?
仅此一次
It's just this one.
朗尼·马尚
Lonnie Machin.
我在达克老巢发现的符号
The symbol that I found in Darhk's lair
跟几个月前马尚留在
is consistent with the symbol that Machin left
两个医护人员尸体旁的符号一致
near the bodies of two paramedics a few months ago.
好吧  可为什么马尚还盯着那些幽灵呢
Ok, but why is Machin still targeting ghosts?
他绑架丹福斯女儿的那次
When he kidnapped Danforth's daughter,
是达克透露了他的藏身之处
Darhk was the one who gave up his location.
这是报复
This is payback.
达克在马尚赶到前就撤走了
Darhk cleared out before Machin got there.
达克比马尚快一步
Darhk is one step ahead of Machin.
然而马尚比我们也快一步
But Machin is one step ahead of us.
好吧  我会一点一点清除障碍的
Yeah. And I'll keep chipping away at my stone wall.
等下
Wait.
你是如何突然发现达克作战基地的
How did you suddenly find darhk's base of operations?
总算在某个审讯中有所发现
Finally had an interrogation that went somewhere.
我要尽可能找出有关马尚的一切信息
I'm going to bring up everything I can on Machin.
我去问问我爸
I'll ask my dad
看星城警局在犯罪现场发现什么线索没有
if SCPD found any leads at the crime scene.
康克林先生
Mr. Conklin.
请解释下这是怎么回事
I trust there was a reason for this?
正如我一直跟你说的
It's like I've been telling you--
奎恩说谎了  他跟我说已经把她干掉了
Queen's a liar. Told me he killed this one.
结果他只是把她藏了起来
Turns out he's just been keeping her stowed away.
你和你手下在营地外想怎么满足自己的需要
What you and your men do to satisfy your needs outside of camp
我都不感兴趣
is no interest of me.
我就猜到你会这么说
I thought you might say that.
正因如此  我才把这些东西也带来了
That's why I made sure to bring these with me.
我看到他俩从沉船残骸里出来
I found these two coming up from a shipwrecked freighter.
这些一定是从里面拿出来的
Must have found them inside.
假如就像他所说的
Now, if he's been on this island
他一直都在这岛上
the whole time like he says...
他又是如何得知这些东西在哪的
How did he know where they were?
那些是我找来给你的
I got those for you.
为满足你们来这里的目的
For...whatever it is you're doing here.
但你却和你声称要杀掉的人...
And yet you waited all this time...
等待了这么长时间
with someone you claimed to kill.
我维护过你  奎恩先生
I've defended you, Mr. Queen.
以我对部下的威望为担保
At the cost of my credibility with my men.
但以后不会了
No more.
你想杀他的话就动手吧
You can kill him now if you'd like.
不
Nah.
我有别的主意
I got something else in mind.
别这么做
You can't do this!
费利西蒂怎么样了
How's Felicity?
还在手术中
She's in surgery.
会花很长时间
It's a long procedure.
我等会儿就要回医院去
I'm going to go to the hospital in a bit,
但我得先回来拿点东西
but I needed to come here and get something first.
拿什么
What?
被你揍的人肯定很惨
I'd hate to see the other guy.
我揍的是安迪
The other guy's Andy.
我们必须要获取达克的信息
We had to get information on Darhk.
我以为那是奥利弗的复仇
I thought that was Oliver's vendetta.
奥利弗是有仇要报
Oliver does have a vendetta.
而我只是想保证朋友们的安全
I'm just trying to keep my friends safe.
你觉得自己受到了背叛
You feel betrayed.
我确实觉得被人背叛了  莱拉
I do feel betrayed, Lyla,
他是我弟弟  我的家人
he was my brother. My family.
我觉得这就是你的问题所在
I think that's your problem.
自从你听说了安迪在阿富汗的所作所为
Ever since you heard about what Andy did back in Afghanistan,
你对安迪的感觉就变了
Andy stopped being Andy to you.
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
他成了叛徒
He became a traitor.
敌人
The enemy.
没错  然后他更加堕落
Yeah, and then he doubled down
成为了达克手下的幽灵
and became one of Darhk's ghosts.
从那以后你就真的把他当成幽灵了
And you've been treating him like a ghost ever since.
这么想你心里就好受了吗
How's that working out for you?
你想说什么  莱拉
What's your point, Lyla?
如果你不想把安迪当成个幽灵
If you're not getting through to Andy as a ghost,
也许你该把他当成自己的弟弟那么对待
maybe you should try reaching him as your brother.
不  不
No. No.
我做不到
I can't do that.
你可以的
Sure you can.
我感受过你对弟弟的爱  约翰
I've seen the love you have for your brother, Johnny.
那爱的力量  无坚不摧
The strength of it. It's iron.
在你放弃安迪之前
Before you give up on Andy,
一定要让他看到我眼中的你
just make sure he sees what I do--
一个为了心爱之人可以走遍天涯海角的男人
A man who'd go to the ends of the earth for the ones he loves.
假如这样有用...
And if it helps...
就把这当成个命令吧  士兵
consider it an order, soldier.
你还好吧
You doing ok?
马尚都回来了  怎么会好
You mean now that Machin's back?
我确定他的目标不是你
I'm sure he's not after you.
怎么可能是我
Why would he be?
我不过是在复活泉水暴怒的驱使下
I only burned his face off
烧毁了他的脸而已
in a fiery fit of Lazarus rage.
西娅...
Thea...
听着  看到奥利拿来的犯罪现场照片上
Look, you know those crime scene photos that Ollie showed us
死了的医护人员和用血画的符号了吗
with paramedics and writing symbols in blood?
不管这人是谁  一定是个怪物
Whoever is out there now is a complete monster.
一个会被我们抓到的怪物
A monster that we're going to catch.
我现在也不确定了
I don't know anymore!
并且最近  我有点分不清何为输赢了
And lately, I can't seem to win for losing.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我们把约翰的弟弟带出蜂巢那天
When we got John's brother out of hive,
我碰到了达米恩·达克
I ran in to Damian Darhk.
他想用他那鬼魔法对付我
And he--he tried to use his creepy magic mojo on me,
可是...
but...
从那以后  我的杀戮欲就少了很多
After that, my blood lust was better.
基本上已经没有了
It was almost completely gone.
我不知道
I don't know,
我只是觉得自己逐渐康复了
I really just thought I was starting to get on the other side of this.
听上去好像你已经没事了
Sounds like you already are.
只是目前马尚出现了
Except now Machin's out there
他也带着杀戮欲望
and he has a blood lust of his own.
这完全是我的错
And it's completely my fault.
不  西娅  别这么想
No, Thea, you can't think that way.
已经晚了
It's far too late for that.
没事的宝贝  没事的
It's all right, sweetheart, it's all right.
老爸
Dad!
你们...在...
What...are you...
我不知道费利西蒂的朋友
I had no idea that Felicity's friend
就是...昆汀的女儿
was...Quentin's daughter.
世界真小
It's such a small world.
非常之小
Microscopic.
西娅  我...一直想让唐娜
Um, Thea, I've been-- I've been trying to get Donna
去餐厅吃点东西
to eat something up at the cafeteria,
但或许你来劝她更好
but maybe you'd have better luck.
对  对
Uh...Yeah. Yeah.
当然  当然  我们走
Sure, sure. Come on.
好的
Yeah, ok.
我...本想说些什么
I was--I was going to say something,
但费利西蒂的事情…
but then everything with Felicity, and...
爸爸...没关系的
Dad, dad... It's fine.
真的吗
Really?
我希望你幸福
I want you to be happy.
奥利弗发现达克的行动基地了
Ok, so Oliver found Darhk's base of operations,
我想你功不可没吧
and I'm guessing that's thanks to you?
如果不能提供情报
Well, there's no use being on the inside
我深入敌方还有什么意义呢
if I can't provide inside intel, right?
达克会发现你在帮绿箭侠的
Darhk's going to realize that you're helping the Green Arrow.
他八成已经猜到了
I think that ship's probably already sailed.
别担心  我能照顾好自己
Don't worry, I can look after myself.
我更担心你
I'm more worried about you.
我以为这问题我们已商量好了
I thought we already worked past this.
一个父亲关心自己女儿
There's no working past a father caring
没得商量
about his daughter.
新女友的短信吗
Hmm, text from the new girlfriend?
行了  走开
Easy, get out of here.
罪证鉴定科
Crime lab.
我手下一半现场调查员都在跟蜂巢的案子
I have half the CSIs I got working on the HIVE crime scene.
我看他们不见得能查到什么
I doubt they'll find anything.
幽灵的DNA都是扰乱过的
The ghosts have their DNA scrambled.
所以这事就更古怪了
Which makes this particularly strange.
马尚涂鸦用的血
The blood Machin used for his graffiti
不是幽灵的
didn't come from the ghosts.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
鉴证科有了比对结果
The CSU got a match.
用的是两个人的血
Two of them, actually.
迈克尔·奥尔金
克里斯蒂儿·奥尔金
迈克尔和克里斯蒂儿·奥尔金
Michael and Crystal Olguin.
马尚的养父母
Machin's foster parents.
三天前被绑架
Kidnapped three days ago.
马尚在算旧账
Machin's settling old scores.
他把他们的血涂在蜂巢里
He planted their blood at HIVE,
显然达克就是他下一个目标
so clearly Darhk is next on his list.
但马尚得有栖身之处  对吧
But Machin's got to be laying low somewhere, right?
你是说他以前的家
You think his former home?
我是说  房子现在空着
Well, I mean, it's vacant now.
对啊  或许我们能黑进他们的安保系统
Yeah, maybe they have a security system we can hack into.
交给我
I've got it.
-还是算了  -我来试试
- Or not. - Here, let me try it.
等等  那人是谁
Ok, wait, who is that?
就是他
That's him.
准备行动
‭Suit up.
真是一点都不奇怪
Well, that's not at all creepy.
前屋没人
Front's clear.
这边也是
Same.
除了有些垃圾  苍蝇
Except for trash, flies,
还有涂鸦
and some bad graffiti.
等等  好像有发现
Wait, I think we might have something.
我在等达克先生的朋友
I was expecting Mr. Darhk's friends,
不过...你们出现真是个惊喜
but...you guys are a pleasant surprise.
尤其是你  亲爱的
Especially you, dear.
别动
Don't move.
真有趣
Funny...
我也想说同样的话
I was going to tell you the same thing.
这是个运动传感器
It's a motion sensor.
干得好
Good.
你以为我会杀了你吗
Oh, did you think I was going to kill you?
我怎么可能杀你
Why would I do such a thing?
是你让我得到自我救赎
You're the one who saved me from myself.
动手吧
Come on, then.
射出你最完美的一箭
Hit me with your best shot.
真不错
Oh, that's pretty.
你是上过美声课吗
Did you take voice lessons?
快走西娅  离她远点
Move, Thea. Stay away from her!
我绝不会伤害她
Oh, I would never hurt her.
不过你嘛...
You, on the other hand...
快手  你没事吧
Speedy, you ok?
现在怎么办
Now what?
弄清楚他都知道些什么
Find out what he knows.
这人是个疯恶棍
Aren't we risking some crazy
我们审问他是不是太冒险了
bond villain stupidity here?
我是说  这人应该被关起来
I mean, this guy needs to be put away.
关到很远的地方
Far, far away.
马尚单靠自己就找到了达克的行动基地
Machin found Darhk's base of operations without any help.
我要知道怎么做到的  和达克现在哪儿
I need to know how; I need to know where Darhk is right now,
我问完就会把他交给警察
and the cops can have him when I am done with him.
马尚神经错乱到极致了
Machin is about ten different kinds of deranged.
你为什么会信他的话
Why would you believe anything he tells you?
因为我没得选
Cause I don't have any other choice.
现在我不想谈这个
Now I am done talking about this.
你们出去吧
Give me the room.
我以为我们已经过了这个阶段了
I thought we've moved past this.
抱歉让你失望了  醒醒
Sorry to disappoint. Wake up.
达米恩·达克在哪里
Where's Damian Darhk?
他回家了
He went home.
我为他筹划了场派对
I was planning a party for him.
你打扰了我的...
You interrupted my--
告诉我他在哪里
Tell me where he is!
不然呢
Or what?
看看我
Look at me.
你还能怎么折磨我
What could you possible do that I haven't already enjoyed?
-出去  -不
- Get out! - ‭No.
听着  有件事你得知道
Look, there's something you need to hear.
什么事
What?!
费利西蒂手术结束了
Felicity's out of surgery.
唐娜刚刚发短信给我
Donna just texted me.
医生没说是什么问题
They didn't say what was wrong.
但我觉得不太妙
But I-- I don't think it's good.
你得去一趟医院
You need to go there.
还要再打吗
Back for more?
打自己的弟弟
Does beating up on your little brother
让你很兴奋吧
give you a little thrill?
我对自己做的事并没感到骄傲  安迪
I'm not proud of what I did, Andy.
其实  我觉得很丢脸
In fact, I'm ashamed of it.
你  约翰  傲慢先生吗
You, John? Mr. High and Mighty?
还记得上次
Do you remember the last time
你打我打到手关节流血吗
you beat on me until your knuckles bled?
记得
Yeah, I do.
那是十年前的事
Ten years ago.
我发现你在贩毒的时候
When I found out you were dealing.
是的  你说服我参军
Yeah. You convinced me to enlist.
像我哥哥一样安分守己
To go the straight and narrow like my big bro.
我试过了
And I tried.
说实话  我真试过了
Honestly, I tried, man.
足以骗过你
Enough to fool you.
我不是那种人
That's just not who I was.
因为这都是为了你自己  约翰
'Cause it's always been about you, John.
因为我让你如此丢脸
'Cause I'm such an embarrassment,
我做的坏事让你难看
and my bad deeds look bad on you.
不  安迪  不是这样的
No, Andy, no, that's not true.
我这么做是因为我爱你  老弟
I did what I did because I love you, man.
是真的  安迪
No, I do, Andy.
以前是  现在也是
Then, now.
安迪  你还是我的弟弟
Andy, you're still my little brother
我还是会熬夜和你玩扑克牌
who I stayed up late playing cards with.
你经历的这些事都是因为我
You're going through this, that's on me.
但你真的以为达米恩·达克会在乎你吗
But do you really think Damian Darhk gives a damn about you?
他相信这个世界需要重置
He believes that the world needs a reset.
说实话  约翰  在我们目睹了阿富汗之后
And honestly, John, after what we witnessed in Afghanistan,
你能说事实并非如此吗
can you tell me otherwise?
好吧
OK.
那你和达克为了拯救世界
All right, so you and Darhk are burning the village
所以放火烧村子  这我明白
in order to save it. I get that.
马尔科姆·梅林也在说同一番话
Malcolm Merlyn was talking the same tune.
但是安迪  达克伤害了我的一个朋友
But Andy, Darhk hurt a friend of mine.
一个非常要好的朋友
A close friend.
一个胜过我和你加在一起的女人
A woman better than you and me put together.
达克是否要拯救世界并不重要
It doesn't matter if Darhk wants to save the world--
但是他做得太过火了
he crossed a line.
所以我请求你  安迪
So I'm asking you, Andy--
求求你  弟弟
begging you, man...
以兄弟的身份
brother to brother.
我在哪能找到达克
Where can I find Darhk?
他
He, um...
喜欢说起斯通黑文
likes to talk about Stonehaven.
说起那里秋日里的落叶
About how the leaves look there...
看起来如何
in autumn.
谢谢你  安迪
Thanks, Andy.
别谢我
Don't thank me.
你以我为耻
You're ashamed.
现在我们互不相欠
Now we're even.
快手
Speedy.
那个一身黑皮衣大嘴巴的
That is what the blonde with the black leather
金发妞是这么叫你的吧
and the big mouth called you, right?
很难正视我  我知道
Hard to look at me, I know.
是你的功劳
Your doing.
我欠你一句谢谢
I owe you a thank you.
战火洗礼  至高无上
Baptism by fire, it's transcendent.
你烧尽了我的软弱
You burnt away my weakness
就像凤凰浴火重生
like a phoenix rising from the ashes.
如果你以为烧毁你的脸很有趣的话
If you thought burning your face off was fun,
那继续说
keep talking.
我会把箭射进你眼睛里
I'll put an arrow through your eye.
那为什么还不动手呢
So why hold back?
我知道你想杀死我
I know you want to kill me.
因为我能控制我自己
Because I can control myself.
不  你不能
No, you can't.
你以为你能  你说你能
Look, you think you can, you say you can,
但是我能从你的双眼里看出来
but I can see it in your eyes.
释放死亡的欲望
The hunger to deliver death.
美味可口
Oh, delicious.
我就说嘛
Told you.
拜  亲爱的
Bye, dear.
唐娜
Hi, Donna.
你去哪了
Where have you been?
我
I...
我应该待在这里的
I should have been here.
西娅说费利西蒂的手术做完了
Thea said that Felicity is out of surgery?
是的  她
Yeah, yeah, she's, uh,
医生对她有了新的诊断
well, she's got a new diagnosis.
什么
What?
他们没法
They can't...
没法治好她
they can't fix her.
他们没法治好她是什么意思
What do you mean, they can't fix her?
她脊椎神经上的损伤
The damage to her spinal cord, it's...
奥利弗  是永久性的
Oliver, it's permanent.
她再也没法走路了
She's never going to walk again.
不  不
No. No.
我们再去看别的医生
We'll talk to another doctor.
不  不  你不...
No, no, no, see, you don't--
我们看的就是别的医生
This-- this is the other doctor, ok?
这位医生专程从中城过来
This is the doctor that came all the way from Central City.
这医生是最好的
This is the doctor.
她人在哪  我要见她
Where is she? I need to see her.
她在恢复室
She's in recovery.
特别报道
We have a special report.
无政府主义者
The anarchist has just been apprehended
刚刚被星城警署逮捕
by the Star City Police Department.
扣押时  地方检察官劳蕾尔·兰斯在现场监督
D.A. Laurel Lance was onsite to oversee his detainment.
住手
Stop!
什么
What?
住手
Stop.
你说把他留给我来处置的
You said he was mine to do whatever I want with.
那是在我看到他肚子上的字迹之前
That was before I saw the signs on his abdomen.
随便你怎么看
Hmm. Well, you can look at it all you want
在他死后
After he's dead.
我还需要他
I have a need of him.
不好  大家退后
No, no, no, everyone stay back.
好吧  我这儿有五支枪对着你
Well, I count five guns.
而你只有一支
And you got one.
你还想耍什么花样
What you going to do?
你跑不掉的
You can't run.
我没打算逃跑
I'm not running.
好久不见
Ah, long time, no see.
我们的谈话还没结束呢
We didn't finish our conversation.
那又怎样  我应该非常感激你
And what, I'm supposed to be so grateful,
打算告诉你据我所知的达克的藏身之处吗
I'm just going to give up what I know about where Darhk is?
绝对不可能
Not likely.
你得确保他必死无疑
You make sure he's dead.
你完全疯了吗
Have you completely lost your mind?
我没时间跟你理论
I don't have time for a debate.
很好
Good,
因为根本没什么好理论的  你所做的
Because there's nothing to debate. What you did--
我做了什么
What I did?
托你的福我只是做了我该做的
I did what I had to do after you made it necessary.
马尚差点就被星城警局逮捕了
Machin was only arrested by the SCPD
因为你告了密
because you gave him up.
你因为某种私人恩怨
You were holding a man prisoner
就放走了一名囚犯
as some sort of personal vendetta!
你知道达米恩·达克和蜂巢
Do you have any idea how many people
在过去的六个月里杀害了多少人吗
Damian Darhk and HIVE have killed over the past six months?
这或许算是仇恨  但绝非私人间的
This might be a vendetta, but it's not personal.
我不知道还会有什么更糟糕的
I don't know what's worse--
你实际上是清楚的  或者你希望我这么想
You actually believe that, or you expect me to.
我在马尚身上放了追踪器
I put a tracker on Machin.
他会带我们找到达克的
He will lead us to Darhk,
那时我们就能一举拿下他们两个
and then we will take both of them down.
要是你这个天才计划没有成功
And when your master plan doesn't work,
你就等于把一个杀人狂送到了大街上
You just sent a murdering psychotic back on the streets.
就像你对莎拉所做的那样
Like you did with Sara.
这不公平
That's not fair.
发生什么了
What's going on?
奥利弗把马尚从羁押车里放了出来
Oliver broke Machin out of custody.
什么
What?
利用马尚找到达克  就这样
Using Machin to get to Darhk, period.
如果你们谁对此还有问题
If either of you has a problem with it,
那就慢走不送
You know where the door is.
劳蕾尔  让我们聊会
Laurel, give us a second.
我没时间听你长篇大论  约翰
I don't have time for a lecture, John.
不是什么长篇大论  奥利弗
There's no lecture here, Oliver,
但是你应该知道安迪给我的有关达克的线索
but you should know that Andy gave me a lead on Darhk
-我一直在调查  -很好  你发现了什么
- and I've been working on it. - Good. What have you found?
很不幸  是个死胡同  但是
Unfortunately, it was a dead end, but--
但是一无所获  一无所获
But nothing. But nothing.
奥利弗  我知道你内心很痛苦  伙计
Oliver, I know you're hurting, man,
但是你要知道
but you should know that whatever
无论你打算怎样  我都支持你
Your play is... I got your back.
但是
But?
但是你这么辛苦走到现在  奥利弗
But you've come so far, Oliver.
你已经重新找回了
You've recovered a humanity
我当初遇见你时
that you lost
你丢失的人性
when I first met you,
我知道你想达克偿还
I know you want payback for what Darhk did
他对费利西蒂犯下的罪恶  而且你也该这么做
to Felicity, and you should.
但最重要的是
But don't lose what made
不要丢失让她倾心于你的本质
her fall in love with you in the first place.
嘿
Oh, hey.
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
我来是想告诉你
I came by to tell you, um...
我做不到
I can't do this.
我的愤怒管理问题
My anger management issues,
它们比我想象的更加难以控制
they are less manageable lean I thought.
听着  我把你正在经历的过程称为愤怒管理
Look, I called what's going on with you anger management
是因为我不知道还能叫它什么
because I don't know what else to call it.
我只知道有什么事在困扰着你
All I know is that there's something that's really bothering you
如果我知道是什么事
and if I know what it is,
或许我能帮上忙
maybe I can help.
你帮不上忙
You can't.
这种情况谁也帮不上忙
This...this can't really be helped.
我不信
I don't believe that.
我一点也不相信
I don't believe that for a second.
西娅  你经受过常人无法忍受的
Thea, you've lived through more tragedies
那些不幸
Than a person has any right to.
你完好无损地站在这  而不是早就被击垮
Instead of crumbling, here you are.
每一天  你都在致力于重建你的家园
Every single day, working to rebuild your home.
你的内心已经变得无比坚强  西娅
You've got steel inside of you, Thea.
这就是你最吸引我的地方
That's what drew me to you in the first place.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我
I'm...
只是还没准备好
just not ready.
好吧  当你准备好了
Well, hey, when you are,
我会在这等你
I'll be here.
好的
Ok.
伙计们
Oh, boy.
我错过什么好戏了吗
What did I miss?
说来话长
That's a long story.
简单点说  马尚逃跑了
Short version-- Machin's gotten loose;
他去寻找达克了  我们正在追踪他
He's after Darhk and we're tracking him.
等等  什么  如果他逃脱了
Wait, what? What happens if he gets out
继续开始伤害大家怎么办
and starts hurting people?
-我也这么想  -没关系
- That's exactly my point. - It doesn't matter.
你口气跟他挺像的
You sound like him.
不  我是说  追踪器没有信号了
No, I mean, the tracker's gone dark.
我们失去了他的信号  他肯定发现了追踪器
I mean, we just lost his signal, he must have found the tracker!
我们弄丢了他
We lost him.
好吧  我们现在知道些什么
Okey so, what we do konw?
不知道
I don't know.
这就是我的全部计划
That was the whole plan.
奥利弗  去看看费利西蒂吧
Oliver, go see Felicity.
现在不是时候  约翰  不是在
Not right now, john, not with--
你要等到什么时候
Then when?
她需要你
She needs you.
现在  我觉得你也需要她
And right now, I think you need her, too.
我们会找到马尚的
We will find Machin.
听着
Look...
他们说的对
They are right, ok?
我们会解决的
We are going to figure this out.
但是现在
But right now,
你得去陪在她身边
you need to go and be with her.
星城医院  急诊处
你好啊  陌生人
Hey, stranger.
抱歉  我没能
Sorry I didn't...
早点来
come by sooner.
我...
It's...
真是不可原谅
It's unforgivable.
除非你是去巴厘岛度假了什么的
Only if you were in Bali or something.
你是去巴厘岛了吗
Were you in Bali?
没有  我...
No, I was, uh...
去巡街了
Beating the streets.
估计有很多人都在找达克
Probably a lot of people looking for Darhk.
我本来不想
I didn't want to come and see you
在抓住达克之前来见你的
until darhk was off the board.
有收获了吗
Any luck?
正在查一些线索
Working some leads.
告诉我你没有失去理智
Tell me you haven't gone off the rails.
这个嘛...
Well...
我只是
I just...
我总忍不住觉得
I can't help but think that...
达克能赢就是因为
the reason that Darhk is winning
我不愿意太出格
is because I haven't been willing to go far enough.
如果我过分了
And that if I was,
如果我出格一些
if I had,
也许你现在就不会躺在这里了
maybe you wouldn't be in here right now.
而且我不知道
And I don't know
如果我不能
what the point...
保护好我身边的人
of what I'm doing as Green Arrow is
那我做绿箭侠还有什么意义
if I can't protect the people that are closest to me.
可是如果你迷失了自我
Well, what's the point of
那么这样还有意义吗
doing it if you lose yourself in the process?
是啊
Yeah.
还有件事我们需要谈谈
There's something else we need to talk about.
那些医生
The doctors...
他们说我...
They say that I'm, uh...
我知道
I know.
我的意思是我们还没有交换结婚誓言
My point being is we didn't really exchange any vows,
所以祸福与共
so the whole for better,
生死契阔这一套还没生效呢
for worse thing doesn't really apply here.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
或许你一直没有来的真实原因
And maybe the real reason you haven't been here
-是因为  -费莉西蒂
- is because... - ‭Felicity.
护士在急诊室里把这个取下来了
The nurse, she took this off of you in the E.R.
好大的胆子
How dare she.
祸福与共  生死契阔
For better, for worse.
好的
Ok.
他在虚张声势
He's bluffing.
瑞特  我可以帮你找到你想要的
Reiter, I can help you find what you need...
但有一个条件
on one condition.
你想怎样
What do you want?
你要保证泰安娜的安全
I want Taiana's safety.
只要她活着
So long as she is alive,
我就好好合作
I'll cooperate.
他是在玩弄你
He's manipulating you.
你觉得他这一段时间都在干什么
What do you think he's been doing this whole time?
你满足他的要求  他就会背叛你
You give him what he wants, he's going to turn on you.
这个协定行还是不行
Do we have a deal or not?
把他们两个带到牢里去
Take them both to prison.
你不能相信他
You can't trust him.
康克林  你记住
Remember, Conklin...
我的计划里
There's no part of my plan
不需要你活着
which requires you to be alive.
你知道吗  我们每天晚上出去
You know, we go out every night...
穿着战衣  冒着生命危险
suiting up, risking our lives,
四处打击刺客和超能力者
fighting assassins and meta-humans
还有所有那些恶人
and all the worst kinds of people.
她却比我们都坚强
She's stronger than all of us.
你这话我完全同意
You won't get an argument from me.
奥利弗  我们可能有了点进展
Oliver, we might have something.
约翰的弟弟说
John's brother said Darhk
达克可能会在一个叫斯通黑文的地方
could be found in a place called Stonehaven.
狄格说那条线索走不通
Dig said that lead was a dead end.
那时我们没有和追踪器的位置对比
That was before we cross referenced the tracker's location
现在找到了一个住宅地址
and came back with a residential address.
马尚要去找达克住的地方
Machin's going after Darhk where he lives.
我们决定出动
We're going to roll out.
我觉得你估计想和我们一起来
I thought...you might want to tag along.
谢谢你
Thank you.
走吧
Let's go.
好啦
All righty.
我刚和达克先生通过话
I just spoke with Mr. Darhk.
他在路上了
He's on his way.
堵车真是麻烦
Traffic's a bitch.
估计要好久呢
Could take a while.
在他来之前  我觉得我们还是可以
I really don't see why we can't have some fun
找点乐子
in the meanwhile.
跟你说明一下
Just so you know,
这不是你的错
this isn't your fault.
是这样  你老爹惹到我了
You see, daddy done me wrong.
总得给我点赔偿吧
There needs to be recompense for that.
我的脸弄成这样
He's not ‭responsible for what--
不是他的错
for what happened to my face.
不直接是  但他促成了
Not directly, but incidentally.
这不就是混乱的意思吗
And isn't that what anarchy is?
看似毫无关联的事情的交集
The intersection of seemingly unconnected events?
这房子的主人是谁
Who owns the house?
这房子是一个空壳公司的
It's owned by a dummy corporation.
没有费莉西蒂我们没办法
Couldn't work through all the layers
看到内部情况
without felicity.
确定马尚在里面吗
And we're sure that Machin's inside?
没错
Oh, yeah.
他在里面
We're sure.
趴下
Get on the ground!
你先是抓了我
First, you catch me.
然后你又放了我
Then, you break me out.
现在你又想抓我
Now, you want to catch me again.
到底想怎样
Make up your mind.
干掉他
Let's take him.
把她们带出去
Get them out of here!
不会有事的
You are gonna be OK!
快走
Come on!
分头行动
Split up.
终于啊
There it is.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你心里有一小部分和我一样
A little piece of me inside of you
正祈求着要出来撒野
just begging to come out and play.
我的家人呢
Where's my family?!
我救了她们
I saved them.
有件事我要说清楚
I want to be clear about something--
我已经无数次证明
I have shown you repeatedly
你无法打败我
that you cannot beat me.
你救了我的家人
You saved my family.
我也会给你几周时间陪陪家人
So I'll give you a few weeks to spend with yours.
好好享受吧
Enjoy your time.
所剩时日不多
What's left of it.
你射偏了
You missed.
还是故意的
On purpose.
我对你很失望
I'm disappointed in you.
达克的妻子和女儿被警方拘留了吗
Are Darhk's wife and daughter in police custody?
她们说自己不是他的家人
They told police they weren't his wife and daughter.
还有假证件之类的
Have fake ID and everything.
快手
Speedy...
你没事吧
You OK?
没事
Yeah.
我只是很抱歉让马尚跑了
I'm just sorry I let Machin get away.
你平安无事我就知足了
I'm just glad that you're all right.
我要去看费利西蒂了
I'm going to go see Felicity.
中国人把这座岛用作监狱
The Chinese use this island as a prison.
我猜你不知道吧
Bet you didn't know that.
据说这里的酷刑比任何地方都凶残
Said being sentenced here was worse than any hell.
大概我要看看自己会不会
Guess I'll just have to see if I can give
比那些中国人更凶狠
those Chinese a run for their money.
瑞特不会一直护着你
Reiter's going to get through with you eventually,
之后我再单独陪你玩
and then you and me will have a little uninterrupted time.
你流了很多血
You've lost a lot of blood.
你不该让伤口这样敞开
You shouldn't let these wounds sit open like that.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你又一次救了我的命
You saved my life again.
真的  不惜自己的性命
Really, at the expense of your own.
我没理由见死不救
Well, you didn't deserve to die.
你是个好人
You're a good man.
我兄弟应该会喜欢你
My brother would have liked you.
我已经把知道的都说了  约翰
I already told you everything I know, John.
我不是来问问题的  安迪
I'm not here to ask you any questions, Andy.
感谢你来
Thank you for coming.
是啊  我...
Yeah, I'm, uh...
很高兴过来
glad I did.
也很高兴你打给了我
And glad you called.
你知道  这有点让我不明白
You know, this is a little bit confusing.
是的
Yeah.
我们先是在一起  然后突然结束
First we're on, then we're off,
现在又...
Now we're...
喝着红酒
Drinking wine.
听着...
Look, um...
今天发生了一些事
Something happened earlier today,
然后
And...
我可能只是想说
I guess I just wanted to say that
你是对的
you were right.
我比想象中更强大
I am stronger than I think I am.
好吧...
Well...
敬你变得更强大
Here's to being stronger, huh?
感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
你坐在这多久了
How long you been sitting there?
不够久
Not long enough.
抱歉我之前走了
Sorry I went away.
我想你已经道过歉了
I think you apologized already.
还远远不够呢
Nowhere near done apologizing.
知道么...
You know...
我想去巴厘岛了
I think I want to go to Bali.
是啊
Yeah.
想和我一起去吗
Want to come with me?
想
Yeah.
你去哪我就去哪
I'd go anywhere with you.
是吗
Yeah?
只有一个问题
Just one question.
什么
Mm-hmm?
达米恩·达克去巴厘岛干什么
What's Damian Darhk doing in Bali?
我这么问  因为只要他还活着
I only ask, 'cause if he's still here,
我们就有任务要做
we have some work to do.
你怎么会这么坚强
How'd you get to be so strong?
我从你那学来的
I took my lead from you.
我把费尔蒙特酒店包了一个月
I've bought out the Fairmount for the month.
在找到新房子前  你们在那是安全的
You'll be safe there until we find a new home.
那个袭击我们的人怎么办
And what about the man that attacked us?
朗尼·马尚
Lonnie Machin?
我绝不让他再伤害你们
He'll never hurt you again.
救我们的是那些治安维持者
Those vigilantes saved us.
我亲爱的瑞文
My dearest Ruve,
你的语气中带有一丝苛责吗
do I detect a note of criticism in your voice?
是的
Yes.
但和你想的不一样
But not the one you think.
你应该今晚就杀了绿箭侠
You should have killed the Green Arrow tonight.
你说了  他救了你一命
As you said, he saved your life.
这时候干掉他有些失礼吧
It would be bad form to take him out now.
创世纪快准备好了
Genesis is almost ready.
现在还周旋太冒险了吧
We're much too close to play games.
还记得我答应过你什么吗
Do you remember what I promised you?
一个新的开始
A new beginning.
你会拥有的
And you will have it.
就在我们把这个世界毁灭以后
Once we've brought this world to its end.
四个月后
布里·索
1936-1981
你还好吗
Are you OK?
你呢
Are you?
不好
No.
你知道该做什么了吧
You know what you have to do, right?
你必须杀了那个混蛋
You have to kill the son of bitch.